

Beata Greń-Onderko beongren@gmail.com (+44) 7448 245462 d.o.b.: 31st August 1963 Polish full driving license CRB on demand

Beata Greń-Onderko

Health care assisant

Career Profile I am a committed, hard working person who wants to make use of her abilites to listen to people, understand their needs, patiently take care and respect them. I have livelong experience in childcare (in Poland, France and UK) but I am willing to learn and participate in professional training for health care assistant, as I have experience in this kind of care. I am full of energy, punctual and open to new challenges.

Key experience During the last summer holiday, I took care of elderly woman, 83 years old. I worked for her voluntarily for two months (after that I had to move to UK). She is completely blind and struggles with diabetes. I helped her almost every day with shopping, household duties and I listened with great pleasure to her life stories or poems she loves to recite. This experience showed me that taking care of elderly people is both for me and for them pleasant, and that it's the job I am called for.

Work experience

September 2015-...

Au pair for two children : girl 22 months, girl 4.5 years old in Ross-on-Wye, UK

October 1986-June 1987

Afternoon babysitting in family orphanage: girl(8 years old); boy (8 years old); girl aged 12 with schizophrenia;

1988-89

24h/7 babysitting of 9-month old baby girl;

July 1990-August 1991

Au pair in Ventabren, France; 2 children: boy aged 1,5 and boy aged 3 as well as taking care of the house (cleaning, cooking, laundry etc.)

Training and Courses

03rd October 1985 -19th May 1986

First aid course at Polish Red Cross at PRC Wrocław

August 1986

One month <u>language scholarship</u> founded by French Embassy at University of Grenoble, France

02nd March 2009-30th June 2009

Training in Social Integration Center (Centrum Integracji Społecznej) in Wrocław. Aim: schooling in licensing and running social cooperative (446 hours)

10th September 2009-19th December 2009

English language course at Pre-Intermediate level in Yellow Language Center Sp. z.o.o (64 hours)

January - August 2010

Participation in "Women professionally active- It's me" project concerning: 60h of <u>UE projects management</u> training, 8h of <u>labour legislation</u> training, 30h of <u>computer skills</u> training (MS Office), 8h of <u>labour market</u> training, 8h of <u>psychology</u> workshop, 8h <u>auto presentation</u> skills training, english language course finished with TOEIC exam

2009-2011

French language course at level B2/C1 in Alliance Français Language School in Wrocław (3 semesters)

October 2014-July 2015

English language course at A2 level (coursebook A2/B1) with final exam

Education

1982-1987

Studies at Faculty of National Economics at Oskar Lange's Academy of Economics (now University of Economics) in Wrocław

Skills and Interests

Languages

Interests

- \circ Natural medicine \circ Sports: fitness and \circ Films and festivals and herbalism skiing
- Gardening Classical music

References

References upon request.